(Penny:)Uh-oh.
What?
(Penny:)It's my boss.
(Penny:)They moved my field ride
up to Monday.
(Amy:)What does that mean?
(Penny:)It means instead
of having a week to study,
(Penny:)I only have two days.
(Bernadette:)That sucks.
(Amy:)Can you start
in the morning?
(Penny:)Uh, it's kind of a lot.
(Leonard:)You know,
let me do a little tonight,
(Penny:)and I'll catch up
with you guys later.
(Bernadette:)You sure?
Yeah, it's okay. Go ahead.
(Amy:)So, um, now that
Penny's not coming...
(Bernadette:)We're not seeing
Fairly Manilow.
Okay.
(dramatic movie music
plays on TV)
(Howard:)Hold on. Pause.
(Howard:)Something doesn't make sense.
Look...
(Howard:)In 2015, Biff steals
the sports almanac
(Howard:)and takes the time machine
(Howard:)back to 1955, to give it
to his younger self.
(Howard:)But as soon as he does that,
he changes the future,
(Howard:)so the 2015 he
returns to would be
(Howard:)a different 2015, not the 2015
that Marty and Doc were in.
This is Hot Tub Time Machine
all over again.